G'ayrat Tangriberganov

Mobile Phone +8
Email ai.

+8210-7714-9308

ai.devveloper@gmail.com harry-kit.github.io **Address**

37, Gwanjeodong-ro 105 beongil, Seo-gu, Daejeon, 201

Short Bio

Web

I am a Researcher in Konyang University Medical Center. Prior to joining the current research center, I spent two memorable years as Graduate student and obtained M.Eng. degree in 2020 from Kumoh National Institute of Technology. My research spans Computer Vision with a focus on Instance Segmentation, Medical Image Generation, and Self-Supervised Learning task

Work Experience

Konyang University Medical Center

Al Researcher Engineer

Daejeon, Republic of Korea August 2020 - Present

- Synthetic Medical Image Dataset Generation for Enhanced Accessibility and Research: Generative Adversarial Networks (StylGAN2-ADA, ProGAN), and Hybrid Diffusion-GAN models, Data Preprocessing, 2D/3D Image Generation and Classification. [project-page]
- A Visual Inspection System Research Designed for Detecting Polyps in Colonoscopy Procedure: Image-Preprocessing, Computer Vision, Object Detection/Segmentation.
- A Research Applied to Effective Feature Extraction using Self-Supervised Learning Methods for Polyps in Colonoscopy Video Footages: Vision Transformer (DINO), Generative Adversarial Network (StyleGAN2-ADA), Image Segmentation (U-Net, ResUNet, ResUNet++), Transfer-Learning. [project-pages]

AiLab

AI/ML Researcher

Gumi, Republic of Korea August 2018 - August 2020

- A Hybrid approach for **Speech** emotion recognition using 1D-CNN LSTM. [Google Scholar]
- Independent projects: **Speech Synthesis**, audio-processing, **TTS**, **STT** [results].
- Image Classification on small datasets in Pytorch. [project-page]

Education

Kumoh National Institute of Technology

M.Eng. in Software Engineering

Tashkent University of Information Technologies in Uzbekistan *M.Sc. in Telecommunication Engineering*

Tashkent University of Information Technologies in Uzbekistan

B.Sc. in Telecommunication Engineering

Gumi, Republic of Korea August 2018 - August 2020 Tashkent, Republic of Uzbekistan August 2015 - August 2017 Tashkent, Republic of Uzbekistan August 2011 - August 2015

Skills

Areas of Expertise

Image-processing, Audio-processing Machine/Deep Learning, Computer Vision (Object Detection/Segmentation), 2D/3D Vision, Generative Adversarial Models, Speech Synthesis, Linux, Pytorch, TensorFlow, Scikit, NumPy, Pandas, OpenCV, etc.

Programming Language Python (OpenCV, Numpy, Dlib, Scikit-learn, Pandas, PIL, Scikit-image, Matplotlib, etc.)

Uzbek (Native), English (Professional), Korean (Basic)